[Music]
hello everyone I hope you're having a
great day today I wanted to talk to you
kind of do like a product review which I
haven't done before so don't judge me
um but Great Lakes gelatin collagen
hydrolysate hydrolysate rather it's
probably backwards for you but you can
see what it is at least this stuff I've
been taking for a few years now and I
actually started out taking the orange
label that one is just regular gelatin
it hasn't been hydrolyzed and so it's
only hot water soluble the orange label
is and you can once it starts to cool
it'll turn into jello or whatever so I
like the green one here because it's
hydrolyzed which means that you can mix
it into hot or cold water without it
gelling up and I have noticed so many
benefits from taking this and you know I
have taken a lot of supplements on and
off throughout the years but I never
really stick with one thing for a long
time but the exception to that is the
gelatin I put it in my coffee every
morning and I notice like if I run out
and I stop taking it for a while
thinking oh it'll be fine right I
noticed a big difference the main reason
I did start taking it is because I had a
torn meniscus several years ago has
probably been 5 years now and I had it I
had surgery on it I had it repaired
right but it still aches so bad no
matter what I do so I noticed that when
I started taking the collagen that it
really took away a lot of that ache
and sometimes I just need to take a
little extra turmeric or something like
that and that combination really pretty
much makes it feel like it's
non-existent so but the gelatin by far
makes the biggest difference for me but
the other benefits that I've noticed are
for hair for skin for nails it just
really helps with the growth and the the
glow the thickness how fast it grows how
hard your nails are how fast they grow
and all I do dishes too much but my
nails are kind of weak but I can tell
when I'm not doing dishes my skin and my
nails and everything are just always
super healthy you know so not to mention
there is 12 grams 11 grams of protein
per serving and a whole bunch of amino
acids good kind of see they're really
high in l-glutamine and just a complete
protein and we know that collagen is
something that's kind of missing from
our diet and I just can't say enough
good things about it especially for
people that have leaky gut or autoimmune
issues or food allergies or
sensitivities where the gut is
compromised collagen can be just a
lifesaver
in terms of going into heal and do a lot
of healing type things for the gut so I
just can't recommend it enough if you're
not already doing it I like to joke with
people I work at a health food store for
those that don't know and I like to joke
with people you know say oh yeah I use
this every day and I'm actually 46 so I
think it's working pretty well and
there's like no way I'm like no not
but I love to see in their reaction
because it's hilarious but I do feel
like it can help be preventative as well
and help with all of your joints all of
you know your skin hair nails your gut
and it's something that just is not in
our diet that actually used to be that
you know our ancestors used to use all
the different parts of the animal where
we get the collagen from you know making
bone broth and things like that that's
another source that you can get collagen
from it is bone broth there's lots of
different ways especially now because
it's becoming a very popular trend so
making sure that you get bone broth and
not like a stock or you know vegetable
broth or something like that you have to
make sure that they're using the bones
and the collagen to get the most
nutrients out of them so considering
that we just don't eat like we used to
it's really important sometimes to
supplement with things like that and I
love getting my nutrients from food I
you know believe in foods I even work at
a health food store and I still you know
I love supplements and vitamins but I
still love to prefer I still prefer to
get my nutrients from food as much as
possible
but this is one of those things that
I've just started taking and I noticed a
big difference with and I can't
recommend it enough so the nice thing
about the green one here the hydrolyzed
Great Lakes collagen is that like I said
you can mix it in hot or cold liquid
it's unflavored so like I said I put it
in my coffee in the morning and I can't
even tell it's there and I've been doing
this for my fiance for the past three
years now three or four years now
probably two and he can tell when he
doesn't take it as well and he's always
like did you put college into my coffee
I was like yes honey I did and he's like
okay good cuz I can tell the difference
if I'm not taking it so um I forget
where I was going with that
but anyway I highly recommend it that's
what her that's where I was going with
it so yes you can mix it into hot liquid
but you can also mix it into cold
smoothies you can mix into yogurt you
can mix it into water or juice its
unflavored and it really doesn't offer a
lot of consistency consistency changes
or flavor changes so that's really nice
about it and the hydrolyzed form seems
to be better for absorption anyway but
it's not going to be the best if you're
wanting to make jello so just keep that
in mind but some people do like to use
it to make jello to get their collagen
in and that's fine too so that's really
all I had today I just wanted to kind of
do a review of some of my favorite
products I'll probably do some more
stuff like this but I I just had to talk
about collagen today and all of the
benefits and I'm sure a lot of you have
been seeing more and more and hearing
more and more about collagen and gelatin
and brunoise bone broth and all of that
and I am just here to say it kind of to
be a testimonial that it's made a big
difference in my life like I said with
my knee pain aches skin hair nails gut
you know digestive help and it just is
super nourishing for me and I've seen a
lot of people you know I don't want to
say heal their gut but they have
improved their gut health a lot with
bone broth and and gelatin it's actually
if you've heard of the gaps diet where a
lot of times you know people have
autoimmune disorders or they have
digestive issues they will in the
protocol they will use bone broth and
collagen and gelatin and these amino
acids and all this good protein to try
to help improve their gut health so that
you no longer have that you know leaky
gut and everything so it's a really
important tool for healing I believe and
I love it so thanks for watching I hope
you guys have a great day
I will talk to you very soon
[Music]
you